<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<xsl:stylesheet version="1.0" xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">
<xsl:output method="html" encoding="utf-8" indent="no" omit-xml-declaration="yes"/>
<xsl:template match="/">
<html><body>

<b>Addressee</b><i> [type the name and address (if applicable) of the recipient]</i>
<br/>
<br/>

<b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//system_date"/></b>
<br/>
<br/>

<b>Subject: </b>Good faith letter
<br/>
<br/>


<b>Dear colleagues,</b>
<br/>
<br/>


The chargeback team is in the process of reviewing the case <xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//appl_id"/> containing the following details:  
<br/>
<b>Case ID: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//dispute_id"/>
<br/>
<b>Merchant name: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//merchant_name"/>
<br/>
<b>Terminal number: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//terminal_number"/>
<br/>
<b>Card number: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//card_number"/>
<br/>
<b>Operation date: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//oper_date"/>
<br/>
<b>ARN: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//rrn"/>
<br/>
<b>Operation amount/currency: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//oper_amount_curr"/>
<br/>
<b>Disputed amount/currency: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//oper_amount_curr"/>
<br/>
<b>RC: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//rc"/>
<br/>
<b>Authorization code: </b><xsl:value-of select="//dispute_appl_data//auth_code"/>
<br/>
<br/>

Your merchant committed a mistake (an error in the amount) while servicing our cardholder. The correct transaction amount should be <i>[specify the amount]</i>. Please find the itemized receipt proving the correct transaction amount.
<br/>
Our cardholder declares the disputed transactions as fraudulent and certifies he/she did not perform them. We have examined the transactions receipts that you sent in response to our retrieval request message and can conclude that the signatures on the receipts are absolutely different. This could be a result of violation of the Visa/MasterCard rules by your merchant. We have listed the card on the stop list and reported the fraudulent transactions properly, according to the Visa/MasterCard rules.
<br/>
<i>[Choose the appropriate variant or type your own variant]</i>
<br/>
Unfortunately, we cannot initiate a chargeback according to the Visa/MasterCard rules, because we do not possess strong enough evidence to support the dispute. Please review this case and contact your merchant to clarify the dispute if possible.
<br/>
Your reply will be very much appreciated.
<br/>
<br/>

<b>Sincerely yours</b>, <br/>
<br/>

<b>Sender’s signature</b> (if required)
<br/>
<b>Sender’s name/surname</b>
<br/>
<b>Sender’s position</b>
<br/>
<b>Sender’s contacts</b>

</body></html>
</xsl:template>
</xsl:stylesheet>
